Manoj Chaurasiya

Sr. Software Developer

Email: manojchrsya@gmail.com | Phone: +91 9987492873

Github: www.github.com/manojchrsya

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working professional with 7+ years of experience Looking for a challenging position in the field of Softwares where my analytical, problem solving skills and application knowledge can be put in for the successful execution of the project.

EDUCATION

I SSC from National High School, Maharashtra Board with a percentage of 74.80 in the year 2005. I HSC from Abhinav Vidya Mandir, Maharashtra Board with a percentage of 73.67 in the year 2007. I Completed B.E in Computer Engineering from S.S.P.M College of Engineering and Technology, Mumbai University with a percentage of 61.37 in the year 2011.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: NodeJs, JavaScript, PHP
Databases: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis, ElasticSearch
Frameworks: ExpressJs, Loopback, StrongLoop

| Web: HTML, CSS, jQuery, VueJs

I Cloud Server : AWS

RECENT PROJECTS

1) DearO - https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.carworkz.dearo

Description - DearO is car and bike workshop management system used by workshop to manage day to day operations in the most effective and efficient manner. **Role and Responsibility**

- Understanding and Analysing the Requirement.

- Developing and Debugging Code as per requirements.
- Creating REST API's for Mobile App.
- Participating in Peer to Peer Code Review

2) CarworkZ - www.carworkz.com

Description - Carworkz is online workshop aggregator platform which is used for mainly booking the appointments for car servicing at near by workshop with minimum price. Role and Responsibility

- Developing and Debugging Code as per requirements.
- Creating REST API's for Mobile App and Web App
- Maintaining existing code base and Website on production.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Working As Sr. Software Developer In MFCS from 5th Dec 2016 to Till Date
- Worked As Sr. Software Developer In Ambab Infotech from 14th Sept 2015 to 1st Dec 2016
- Worked As Php Developer In PSP Marketing from 26th Jul 2014 to 10th Sept 2015
- Worked As Php developer In Postbox Communication from 26th Feb 2013 to 25th jul 2014
- l Worked As **Software Trainee Engineer** In Intelliswift from 19th March 2012 till 25th feb 2013.

ACHIVEMENTS

| Spot award at Mahindra First Choice Services. (November - 2018)